As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices.
We take in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try.
Get ready to roam.
So all aboard now, we're set to go.
Set sail to the ocean so deep.
Ready for a truly grand adventure.
Well, don't you think
that sounds really fun.
All this excitement is second to none.
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices.
We take in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace.
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices.
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud.
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous.
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
The same time I think so this swordsman
can project his attacks as well that.
Samurai zombies using the power of my
shadow to move around right now but.
Before his death he must have been an
incredibly strong man which means the.
Combination of his strength my technique
will make him quite formidable indeed.
Are you trying to say that those two
dead even I'm saying these two swordsmen.
Have an incredible amount
of destructive power at
their command and as such
I don't think this fight.
Will last long prelude
of them he's trying to
break my sword two sword
style flash demon bear.
Hmm?
Shabbat!
Born them all!
Two-sword-style draw!
Rush him on!
Yeah!
He took the hit.
They cut through the pillar?
Easy! Whoa!
This floor, it's gonna
break apart! What do we do?
That's it!
We're out of here!
Hang on, this place has fallen to pieces!
72-caliber Phoenix!
Polka-releezer!
Weapons left!
Oh, that was a close one.
Watch out!
You're going to fall!
Oh, crap, I'm going to slip.
Well, even without a foothold.
If this goes on much longer,
my sword's going to break.
This guy doesn't just have the
strength of that legendary samurai.
He's got his wits, too.
One-sword style!
Flying dragon!
Reverse humming.
Aramont Slash!
Blaze!
What?
Who won't cut fire?
My defeat.
The legendary owner of this
blade may have long since falling
But its story does not end
here With you as its master,
this sword will surely be satisfied
You hear that?
It sounded like the
samurai said something.
And I couldn't understand him?
What in the hell's going on here?
What's going on? In short,
it looks like the battle between them is
over I've seen many fights in my life,
but none quite like this.
Hot Samurai, he scarcely used a fraction
of his strength when he was fighting me.
Such an impressive battle.
This body of a legendary samurai.
How shameful of me to
allow it to no defeat.
As long as you feel shame, it's enough.
You're a true swordsman in
body and spirit, aren't you?
I wish I could have met you in your era.
It's back, finally!
After five long years, my shadow is back!
I'll take this sword like I said, but let's
pretend like this fight never happened.
Samurai from Wano
How does it feel to be captured
by the power of your own friends?
Yeah, and this one use some dumb
trick to try and feed me some salt
I can't believe Sanji's so far gone
already that he would kick Robin like that.
You're not our friend anymore.
You're just a zombie.
Who's this Sanji you keep talking about?
No one can save you now.
Fuss, fuss, fuss.
I hate to be the bearer of bad tidings,
but these two might not have any
memory of beating your friends left.
Upon creation,
some zombies retain a small
sense of their former selves,
but the new body and
soul soon synchronize.
Not even a shred of humanity remains.
They all become obedient zombies
that follow my every command.
For a zombie following orders
is the pinnacle of existence!
You finally convinced me you're an
evil man all the way to the core?
hog back
In the past you were responsible
for saving so many lives.
I really looked up to you as
a humanitarian and a doctor.
I didn't even mind your
research on zombies
Seeing as how death
can happen so suddenly,
those who die and those who are left behind
always leave so many things left unsaid.
Things that they'll never
have a chance to say again.
If there was some way to bring
the deceased back to life,
even for only a moment, that brief
time could be spent finding closure.
Even if people called
you a heretic or a mad
scientist and announced
all the work you did.
It would have been worth
it to heal people's hearts.
That's why when you said
you had spent years in
this place researching
how to resurrect the dead.
I believed you were doing it
with the best of intentions.
False. False. False. Fool.
Who would go to that much
trouble to help others?
Your naivete is astounding.
This is the way it's always been.
I'm a genius who deserves the best.
Money was the driving force
behind using my skills.
But my notoriety led patients from
all over the world to my doorstep.
There were too many needy little whiners.
Save my father, please save my child.
Save my sweetheart, nag,
nag, nag, what a bother.
It was so annoying.
I was expected to carry
the burden of all the
incompetent doctors
who couldn't help them.
Are you starting to understand
the horrors of being a genius?
If you wish to idolize me for my
work in the medical field, fine.
But you have no right to
say you're disappointed in
me if my motives don't live
up to your precious ideals?
Then you can just kiss my
ass you stupid reindeer.
How dare you preach to
me on how to be a doctor?
That's not what I'm
trying to do you bastard.
I'm trying to tell you.
I don't even accept
you as a doctor anymore
I don't accept these zombies either.
They're already dead, yet you
still have control over them.
You won't let them rest in peace!
You've made a mockery of human life!
What a narrow-minded thing to say.
I gave them a new life, and yet you think
they should just be rotting in the ground?
Yes, I do!
You're missing the
scientific breakthrough.
I gave them life after
death. Don't you see?
How can you simply overlook
the value of that life?
AVAILABLE!
Don't move.
Now, while you're down
there, lick the floor.
Yes, Master Hogback.
You saw that room, didn't you, Dr. Chumpa?
That was actually my room.
The photos on the wall are of a deceased
stage actress named Victoria Shandora.
I was infatuated with her and her
charm for as long as I can remember.
Her beauty and allure
captured not only my heart,
but the hearts of men
all over the country.
Now it's as good as new, Doctor.
How embarrassing!
I can't believe one of my
patients sewed a button on for me!
I'm just happy to help.
She was popular without conceit.
She was kind and loving to her family.
She was a wonderful woman thoughtful and
generous to everyone, but unfortunately?
She was also spoken for after I made
my mark as a doctor I proposed to her.
But as she was already
engaged, she refused.
I heard the terrible news
about what had happened to her.
She had suffered a fatal accident.
I was at a loss for words.
In the end, I left my job behind.
That's when he found me.
He appeared out of nowhere with
the solution to everything.
My master, Gecko Moria.
I could use a man of your talent.
Linda, too, made Dr. Hog back.
I accepted his offer and boarded
his ship on one condition!
That he, combining his amazing
abilities with my own,?
would help me bring my
Shandora back to life.
I missed you, my love.
I stole her corpse in order to obtain a
Shandora that would belong
to and obey only me.
She's alive! Yes!
I wish every last plate in the
world would disappear What?
Her personality had changed and it
certainly wasn't for the better.
However, she was still beautiful.
And frankly, that was
all the matter to me!
I'm happy and I'm sure she is as well.
I've given her a second life.
A chance to rejoin this world
as a living human being.
You call that a living human being?
Tell her to stop that! Now!
A human being whose heart and body
have been separated is no human at all!
You took a corpse that had
no choice in the matter
and turned it into nothing
more than a monster!
Every time you make
one of these creatures,
There's somewhere there's
a human you've devastated
with pain and sorrow and I
can't let you go unpunished!
And what would a stupid
reindeer pirate doctor with
such limited medical skill
possibly know about life?
Shinri, rise!
Rise and kill them all!
Yes.
Now, you two are next on the zombie list.
You should be happy, Dr. Chopper.
You may die, but once you're brought back
you'll be the assistant of the doctor.
You've idolized so much
square plate blades
Stop it
False, false, false.
Don't let her size fool you.
Despite her petite figure, I've
modified her to be a killing machine.
Listen, Shandora, you don't have
to take orders from that maniac.
You...
I'll kill you.
I feel so bad for you.
Look what Hogback's done to you.
What would your family say
if they knew about all this?
Let go of me.
You've been stitched together like a
ragdoll, forced to serve as an undead slave.
Your loved ones would be mortified.
Okay, unhand me.
You were born with both a body and a
soul, but that soul died a long time ago.
And yet your body is being
forced to follow orders.
Where's the meaning in that?
Force, force, force, force.
Don't tell me you doubt
your own eyes, Doctor.
This is what humans
have always dreamed of.
Resurrection of the dead.
Man can live again.
Just because it moves
doesn't make it alive.
To be alive, you've got to be free!
You're treating her like she's nothing!
Anything that exists like
that can't be a human being!
Darkma Tackle! Help her! Quickly!
Save Century!
Kill the others!
Oh, no! Chopper!
Gleason style, 108!
All about me!
Zoro, stop it!
Now, don't save Fleur!
My master said, kill the others!
Careful with that attack
you almost killed me.
Stay the hell out of my way!
You're in my way.
I was doing fine till you saw.
Master told me to kill the others.
Yes I know that we have
the same master you idiot.
Now back off.
You back off.
He said kill the others
I'll start with you.
Cut it out!
What the hell are you idiots doing stop
fighting now we need to work together right.
Can't give orders if you
can't talk if the others
are everyone but Shandora
who knows what could end
up happening even without
any trace of their old
memories those two just
can't seem to get along.
No matter what they do.
This tower is rather tall isn't
it huh if only we were under
your power you could kill us
by asking us to jump out of it.
Huh?
How dare you speak to
me that way you'll be
under my control once I
turn you into zombies and!
Once I do I'll say jump off this
tower and put an end to yourself?
Yes, master! Oh!
No way! That was a mistake!
As for us, we'd rather not.
Oh no, dammit!
You pathetic excuses
for humans tricked me!
I'm supposed to be a genius!
Now, once Luffy's dealt with Moria,
all the zombies he created on
this island will be purified,
which means the only thing left for
me to do around here is kick your ass!
Century, listen!
I need you to buy some
time while I escape!
Hey!
Didn't you hear me? Get them!
It doesn't matter if they purify you,
I can just give you another shadow!
My body...
It won't move.
What? Send me!